U.S. Emergency Board No. 174 Records 5006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board No. 174 Records
1952-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board
5006
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Transcripts and exhibits of the United States Emergency Board No. 174, pertaining to the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, and the National Railway Labor Conference.
3110773
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 21, 2002
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5007: U.S. Emergency Board No. 175 Transcripts and Exhibits 5012: Saul Wallen Papers 5027: U.S. Emergency Board No. 178 Transcripts 5030: U.S. Emergency Board No. 179 Exhibits and Related Material 5036: U.S. Emergency Boards under the Railway Labor Act Reports 5037: U.S. Emergency Board No. 81 Records 5038: U.S. Emergency Board No. 94 Records 5039: U.S. Emergency Board No. 98 Records 5040: U.S. Emergency Board No. 106 Records 5042: U.S. Emergency Board No. 111 Records 5043: U.S. Emergency Board No. 114 Records 5044: U.S. Emergency Board No. 116 Reports and Exhibits 5045: U.S. Emergency Board No. 118 Records 5046: U.S. Emergency Board No. 119 Records 5047: U.S. Emergency Board No. 120 Records 5048: U.S. Emergency Board No. 121 Records 5050: U.S. Emergency Board No. 124 Records 5051: U.S. Emergency Board No. 125 Records 5052: U.S. Emergency Board No. 129 Records 5053: U.S. Emergency Board No. 130 Records 5054: U.S. Emergency Board No. 133 Exhibits 5055: U.S. Emergency Board No. 134 Records 5056: U.S. Emergency Board No. 135 Records 5057: U.S. Emergency Board No. 137 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5058: U.S. Emergency Board No. 138 Records 5059: U.S. Emergency Board No. 142 Records 5060: U.S. Emergency Board No. 145 Records 5061: U.S. Emergency Board No. 146 Records 5062: U.S. Emergency Board No. 154 Records 5064: U.S. Emergency Board No. 169 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5075: U.S. Emergency Board under the Taft Hartley Act Records 5579: National Mediation Board Emergency Board 180, Train Crew Consists 5934: Arthur Stark Papers on the President's Emergency Board #219
Collective bargaining -- Railroads -- United States -- History -- Sources; United States. Emergency Board No. 174.
3110773
- Supplement to the Opening Statement (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Railroad Safety Statistics (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Methods of Computing Average Earnings and Rates From Interstate Commerce Commission Statistics (Box 1, Folder 3)
- General Wage Issue (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inequity Adjustments For Conductors (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Daily Bate of Mechanics and Minimum Daily Rates of Through Freight Conductors (Box 1, Folder 5a)
  Scope and Contents
  (two copies)
- Productivity of Transportation Employees (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Increased Speed, Length, and Weight of Trains (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Graduated Rates of Pay (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Four Representative Meals and Lodging Agreements (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Away-From Home Expenses (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Leisure Time Issues and Sick Leave (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Railway Financial Statistics (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Average Straight-time Hourly Earnings of all Railway Employees and Unit Labor Costs - Class I Line-Haul Railways, 1952-1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Wage Stabilization Board Washington, D.C. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Excerpt From Address by E. Sid Willis, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Manager of General Electric Company's Employee Benefits and Practices Service, at the Southeastern Personnel Conference at Duke University, April 3, 1964 Recent Changes in Retirement, Other Fringe Benefits
- Excerpts From "Employee Benefits, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  United States Chamber of Commerce
- Average Straight-Time Hourly Earnings of all Railway Employees and Unit Wage and Related Costs Class L Line-Haul Railways, 1952-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Excerpts From Text of President Nixon's Press Conference, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  27-Jan-69
- The Proposals of the Parties and the Appearances for the Carriers (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Supplement to the Opening Statement (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Statement of J. P. Hiltz, Jr., Chairman, National Railway Labor Conference (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Safety Responsibility of Engineers and Conductors (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Technological and Operational Improvements (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Report of the Presidential Railroad Commission (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Award of Arbitration Board No 282 and Opinion of the Neutral Members (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Report of the National Joint Board (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Report of Emergency Board No. 126 and Opinion and Award of Arbitration Board No. 255 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Affidavit of Allister R. McRae (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Affidavit of T. B. Wagner (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Affidavit of Ernest E. Walters (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Summary of Results of Survey Covering Duties Performed by Locomotive Engineers (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Representation, Wages and Wage Costs (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Economic Conditions in the Railroad Industry (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Post World War II Changes in Gross Product and Selected Components Thereof (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Supplemental Material (Box 1, Folder 35)
- The 1967 - 1969 Pattern (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Pay Supplements (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Holiday Pay (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Vacations With Pay (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Paid Sick Leave (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Away-From-Home Expenses Held-Away-Prom-Home-Terminal Rule (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Submission Exhibit Carrier Proposals (Box 1, Folder 42)
- 11-7-66 to 9-14-68, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 43)